<?xml version="1.0"?>  
<!-- This XML data file is only a dummy one which can by replaced by the real internect data in the future. 2014-3-26-->
<feed xmlns="http://www.chinacoal.com" xmlns:georss="http://www.chinacoal.com">  
  <updated>2014-03-25T04:41:18Z</updated>  
  <title>USGS M2.5+ News List</title>  
  <subtitle>Real-time, the news list for Dolphin project.</subtitle>  
  <link rel="self" href="http://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/catalogs/1day-M2.5.xml" mce_href="http://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/catalogs/1day-M2.5.xml"/>  
  <link href="http://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/" mce_href="http://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/"/>  
  <author><name>Kevin</name></author>  
  <id>DolphinList</id>  
  <icon>/favicon.ico</icon>  
  <entry>  
      <id>2014032501</id>  
      <title>Ronaldo should stop complaining</title>  
      <updated>2014-03-25T04:14:03Z</updated>  
	  <image>newsdemo1</image> 
      <brief>Gerard Pique has hit back at Cristiano Ronaldo in the wake of the Real Madrid attacker's claims that the referee favored Barcelona in the Catalans' 4-3 La Liga win on Sunday.</brief>  
      <content>Gerard Pique has hit back at Cristiano Ronaldo in the wake of the Real Madrid attacker's claims that the referee favored Barcelona in the Catalans' 4-3 La Liga win on Sunday.
Referee Undiano Mallenco played a leading role in the enthralling encounter at the Santiago Bernabeu as he awarded three penalties over the course of the game - two to Barcelona and one to Madrid - and sent off Sergio Ramos, prompting Ronaldo to accuse the official of bias toward the Catalans. 
However, Pique has stressed that Ronaldo should not be looking for excuses given that the Portugal star was awarded a controversial penalty after being tripped by Dani Alves outside the box.</content>  
      <category label="Age" term="Past hour"/>  
  </entry>  
     <entry>  
      <id>2014032502</id>  
      <title>New demo</title>  
      <updated>2014-03-24T04:14:03Z</updated>  
	  <image>newsdemo2</image> 
      <brief>Inside Kim Kardashian and Kanye West's Private Time with Baby North</brief>  
      <content>In return, she and Kanye West gave the fashion magazine an up-close-and-personal look into their life at home with their daughter, North.</content>  
      <category label="Age" term="Past hour"/>  
  </entry> 
       <entry>  
      <id>2014032503</id>  
      <title>Hit the Jackpot</title>  
      <updated>2014-03-23T04:14:03Z</updated>  
	  <image>newsdemo3</image> 
      <brief>Hit the Jackpot in Your Search for a New Car</brief>  
      <content>Give Yahoo! Autos a spin - for the web's best news, reviews, and research on hundreds of new makes and models.Don't smoke? Doesn't matter. You could still be doing damage to your long-term health.The following six unhealthy habits either expose you to the same contaminants in cigarette smoke or lead to cancer rates equivalent to those caused </content>  
      <category label="Age" term="Past hour"/>  
  </entry> 
  <entry>  
      <id>2014032504</id>  
      <title>Judge Joe Brown Arrested</title>  
      <updated>2014-03-22T04:14:03Z</updated>  
	  <image>newsdemo4</image> 
      <brief>Judge Joe Brown Arrested and Jailed in Tennessee For Contempt of Court</brief>  
      <content>Judge Joe Brown was arrested and jailed in Memphis, Tenn., on Monday, March 24 -- find out what happened!How much cash do you have hidden around your home? If the answer is more than $100, then you have too much cash in your house. We all keep a little money on hand for those rare occasions</content>  
      <category label="Age" term="Past hour"/>  
  </entry> 
    <entry>  
      <id>2014032503</id>  
      <title>Is This the Most Glamorous Post-Birth Photo — EVER?!</title>  
      <updated>2014-03-21T04:14:03Z</updated>  
	  <image>newsdemo5</image> 
      <brief>But look above at heiress Tamara Ecclestone - daughter of billionaire and Formula</brief>  
      <content>But look above at heiress Tamara Ecclestone - daughter of billionaire and Formula One Management CEO Bernie Ecclestone - who gave birth to her daughter Sophia at the London's private Portland Hospital (a favorite among celebs) a couple of days </content>  
      <category label="Age" term="Past hour"/>  
  </entry> 
</feed>